Guide to the Susie Bright papers and On Our Backs records, 1978-2013.
Bright, Susie papers and On Our Backs records
- Periodicals
  - Susie Bright Related Periodicals
    - Hustler, March 1986 (Box 21)
      Includes an article by Susie Bright "Real Live Dyke", "Confessions of a Teenage Lesbian."
      Volume/Issue: Volume 12, Number 9
      Publisher: Hustler Magazine Inc.
    - Lesbian and Gay Film Festival: San Francisco, June 17-26, 1988 (Box 21)
      Susie Bright is listed as being on the festival screening committee.
      Publisher: Frameline Production
    - On Our Backs, Summer 1988 (Box 21)
      Signed on the cover by Kitty Tsui "Dear Debi, Thanks for the photo op! Kitty."
      Volume/Issue: Volume 5, Number 1
      Publisher: Blush Entertainment
    - Penthouse Forum, August 1977 (Box 21)
      Includes article by Honey Lee Cottrell, "How Women Make Love to One Another."
      Volume/Issue: Volume 6, Number 11
      Publisher: Forum International Ltd.
    - Penthouse Forum, January 1989 (Box 21)
      Includes article by Susie Bright, "Two Days on a Porn Se.t"
      Volume/Issue: Volume 18, Number 5
    - Penthouse, March 1998 (Box 21)
      Advance Copy, possibly contains content by Susie Bright, this is unclear.
      Volume/Issue: Volume 29, Number 7
      Publisher: General Media Communications, Ltd.
    - The Red Tide, Summer 1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      High School community Information Service newspaper. Includes article by Sue Bright from Uni High, "Police Brutality Hits Brentwood" she is also listed as a contributor.
      Volume/Issue: Volume 3, Number 3
    - Shrimp, ca. 1993 (Box 21)
      Signed inside the cover by "Dear Susie, I'm going to play jump rope with your vulva. Loves desires, Ms. Vaginal Davis", publisher and editor-in-chief.
      Volume/Issue: Debut Issue
    - Stormy Leather, 1989 (Box 21)
      Leatherwear catalog, features photos of Susie Bright, Honey Lee Cottrell, Fanny Fatale.Volume/Issue: 1989 Edition
      Publisher: Stormy Leather
    - Utne Reader, January - February 1995
      "Susie Bright is mentioned in the article "100 Visionaries Who Could Change Your Life"Volume/Issue: Number 67
  - Miscellaneous Periodicals
    - A för Amazon, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Author/Editor: Marianne Nilsson
      Volume/Issue: Volume 1, Number 2
    - Buck Rogers #5, Sunday pages from No. 49-60., 1981 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Large format volume of comic reprints.
      Volume/Issue: Number 5
      Publisher: Club Anni Trenta
    - California Living Magazine, April 15, 1984 (Box 21)
      Author/Editor: Harold I. Silverman
      Publisher: San Francisco Examiner
    - High Performance, Winter 1979-1980 (Box 21)
      The Performance Art Quarterly
      Volume/Issue: Volume 2, Number 4
      Author/Editor: Linda Burnham
    - Pages from Hustler, ca. 1980 (Box 21)
      A vibrator advertisement by Leasure Time Products [sic] and an Anti-Smoking Advertisement.Volume/Issue: Number 52, Fall 1986
    - Leatherwomen Calender, 1988 (Box 21)
      Author/Editor: J. C. Collins and Sky Renfro
    - Loompanics Unlimited; Sellers of Unusual Books, 1991 (Box 21)
      Volume/Issue: 1991
      Publisher: Sellers of Unusual Books
    - The North Star: Sex Wars, Fall 1986 (Box 21)
      Volume/Issue: Number 4
      Publisher: North Star Network
    - Temporary Hoarding: Rock Against Racism (Box 21)
    - Whole Earth Review, Fall 1986 (Box 21)
      Volume/Issue: Number 52